customercarecontacts.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Customer Care Contacts

Thank you for visiting Customer Care Contacts. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the webite, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions.

**Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees have access to this information.

**Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Comments**  
All comments or forum postings posted on customercarecontacts.com is available for public to read. However, we do not disclose in any section your email address or any other details that might not be related to data on our website. Please be informed that some responses posted for comments is that of Customer Care Contacts team and is not attested by the respective company or service provider.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may reach us using the contact us page at the bottom of the website.
